carcraft.co.uk 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Carcraft.co.uk

EGFV RIX Limited trading as Carcraft (Company number. 9693284) (“ **We** ”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. 

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.carcraft.co.uk you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. 

## Information we may collect from you

The information below provides an overview of how we protect your privacy whenever you are on this site. Personal information on the website may be gathered in two ways as follows: 

  * indirectly (for example, through cookies - see section "Our use of Cookies"); and/or 
  * directly (for example, when you provide information on various response forms). 

This information includes your internet address so that we can track unique visits to our site for analytic purposes. 

We collect information when you choose to submit it to us. Throughout our site, we may provide opportunities for you to apply for various products and services for example car data checks and valuations. When we collect this type of information, we will notify you of the reason we are asking for information and how this information will be used. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it. 

We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, third party car dealers, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them. The purposes for which we may use such information are as set out below (See section: **Uses made of the information** ) 

## Our use of Cookies

Cookies are small text files based on your hard drive each time you access a website. We may use cookies to facilitate your internet sessions, to maintain security and to improve our websites. In particular we use Google Analytics’ cookies to measure use of and improve our website and support advertising features as detailed below. 

You can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options in your menu browser. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site and by continuing to use our site you consent to the use of cookies. 

Please refer to our Cookie Policy for further information on the types of cookies we use. 

## About Google Analytics Advertising Features

This website implements and uses Google Analytics Advertising Features which includes the following: 

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics;
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting;
  * DoubleClick Platform integrations;
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. These cookies are used to collect data about the websites and individual pages that users visit and are typically used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests, and to help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. For further details of these cookies please refer to our Cookie Policy. 

You can find out more information about how Google uses you data by reading Google’s privacy policy located: at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners. 

You can opt-out or customise the use of Google Analytics Advertising Features via Ads Settings found at: www.google.com/settings/ads. This lets you opt out of ads shown to you based on factors such as your interests, previous visits to other websites, and demographic details on your computer’s browser. You can also prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics by downloading the Google Analytics’ Opt-out Browser Add-on, which can be found at: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

We will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google adverting product or feature without your prior affirmative consent. 

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

_Information you give to us. We will use this information:_

  1. to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
  2. to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
  3. to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you (only if you have consented to this);
  4. to notify you about changes to our service;
  5. to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 

_Information we collect about you. We will use this information:_

  1. to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  2. to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 
  3. to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  4. as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
  5. to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
  6. to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

_Information we receive from other sources._

  * We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

## Disclosure of your information

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. 

We may share your information with selected third parties including: 

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If EGFV RIX Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of EGFV RIX Limited our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## How we protect your information

The internet is not a secure medium. We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your personal data wherever it may be in EGFV RIX Limited. The open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. However, we aim to apply appropriate levels of security at all times. 

EGFV RIX Limited does not knowingly collect data nor market to children anywhere. 

## Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [info@carcraft.co.uk](mailto:info@carcraft.co.uk). 

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

## Access to information

Individuals can find out if we hold any personal information by making a ‘subject access request’ under the Act. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. 

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [info@carcraft.co.uk](mailto:info@carcraft.co.uk).
